A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, The Fund for the Advancement of Education (TFAE) files FA740
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Awardees – Educational Institutions, 1947-1976; II; 92.4 Cubic Feet 77 boxes.
  - Grant Files, 1948-1976; 1; 51.6 Cubic Feet 43 boxes.; 43 boxes.
    - Edsel Ford High School Program - A Project in Secondary Education Curriculum Development, 1962 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Records Bureau - TFAE Grant 1971 - General Support Grant - Attachments, 1961-1971 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Records Bureau - TFAE Grant 1971 - General Support Grant, 1971-1972 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Records Bureau - TFAE Grant 1972 - Recoverable Grant - Attachments, 1971-1972 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Records Bureau - TFAE Grant 1972 - Recoverable Grant, 1971-1972 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Testing Service Development of New Approaches to Identify Learning Abilities of First Grade Pupils from Diverse Sociocultural Backgrounds - Grant 65, 1965-1967 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Testing Service Lay Readers - Grant 61, 1961 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Testing Service Lay Readers - Reports, 1963 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Testing Service - PS Student - Writing Ability - Grant 1958-1959 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Testing Service - PS Student - Writing Ability - Grant, 1957 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Testing Service - PS Student - Writing Ability - Progress Report, 1956-1959 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Educational Testing Service - PS Student - Writing Ability - Proposal & Grant, 1955-1956 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Elmira College (College Center of the Finger Lakes) Utilization of Library Facilities - Grant 62, 1962-1964 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Elmira College (College Center of the Finger Lakes) Utilization of Library Facilities - Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Emory University Better Utilization of Programmed Instruction - Grant 63, 1963-1965 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Emory University Masters of Arts in Teaching Program - Grant, 1960-1961 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Emory University Graduate Institute of the Liberal Arts - Grant 54, 1954 (Box 11 (49572))
    - Encyclopedia Britannica Films - Better Utilization of Teachers Revolving Fund - Grant, 1956 - 1963 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Encyclopedia Britannica Films - Better Utilization of Teachers Revolving Fund - Planning, 1957 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Encyclopedia Britannica Films - Better Utilization of Teachers - Revolving Fund - Report (including White Report evaluation), 1956 - 1959 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Esalen Institute - Attachments, 1967 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Esalen Institute - Grant, 1967 - 1968 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Eugene Public Schools - School Improvement - General Correspondence, 1960 - 1962 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Eugene Public Schools - Grant, 1960 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Eugene Public Schools - School Improvement - Report, 1960 - 1965 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Eugene Public Schools - School Improvement - Grant 62, 1960 - 1966 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Eugene Public Schools - School Improvement - Reports, 1962 - 1968 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Eugene Public Schools - School Improvement - Reports, 1960 - 1962 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Evanston Township High School District - Grant 66, 1966 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Evanston Township High School District - Reports, 1966 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Fashion Institute of Technology Preventive Maintenance - Grant 63, 1963 - 1966 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Fashion Institute of Technology Preventive Maintenance - Reports, 1963 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Fisk University - Equal Education - Bi-Racial - Conference on High School/College Chemistry Teaching, 1954 - 1955 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Fisk University - Equal Education - Bi-Racial - Conference on High School/College Chemistry Teaching - Reports, 1955 (Box 12 (49573))
      - [Untitled], 2014.015.008; Still Image (Box SF2)
    - Florida Presbyterian College - Ruml Plan - General Data, 1959 - 1960 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida Presbyterian College - Ruml Plan - Grant 61, 1961 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida Presbyterian College - Ruml Plan - Supplemental Grant 62, 1962 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida Presbyterian College - Ruml Plan - Publicity, 1962 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida Presbyterian College - Ruml Plan - Reports, 1962 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, University of - Utilization - Revolving Fund - General Data, 1957 - 1959 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, University of - Utilization - Revolving Fund - Grant, 1957 - 1967 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, University of - Utilization - Revolving Fund - Supplementary Grant, 1957 - 1959 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, Board of Control - Improvement in Curriculum - Grant, 1958 - 1961 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, Board of Control - Improvement in Curriculum - Planning, 1959 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, Board of Control - Improvement in Curriculum - Report, 1961 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, University of - Grant 66, 1965 - 1968 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, University of - Utilization - Revolving Fund - Publicity, 1957 - 1958 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, University of - Early Child Stimulation Through Parent Education - Report, 1969 (Box 12 (49573))
    - Florida, University of - Report, 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Florida, Univerity of - Report - Final, 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Fordham University - An Experiment in Teacher Education - The Experimental and Developmental Master of Science in Education Program in Secondary Education for Graduates of Liberal Arts Colleges - Grant & Proposal, 1957 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Fordham University - An Experiment in Teacher Education - The Experimental and Developmental Master of Science in Education Program in Secondary Education for Graduates of Liberal Arts Colleges - Publicity, 1957 - 1958 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Fordham University - An Experiment in Teacher Education - The Experimental and Developmental Master of Science in Education Program in Secondary Education for Graduates of Liberal Arts Colleges - Reports, 1957 - 1960 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Four Massachusetts Colleges - Grant [CONFIDENTIAL - Resume], 1957 - 1961 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Four Massachusetts Colleges - Grant, 1954 - 1956 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Four Massachusetts Collegs - Publicity, 1957 - 1959 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Four Massachusetts Colleges - Report, 1961 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Four Massachusetts Colleges - Report, 1956 - 1960 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Frederick County, Board of Education - Travel and Study - Grant 65, 1965 - 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Frederick County, Board of Education - Travel and Study - Reports, 1966 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Freeport Public Schools - Travel and Study - Attachments, 1966 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Freeport Public Schools - Travel and Study - Grant 66, 1966 - 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Freeport Public Schools - Travel and Study - Reports, 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Fremont Unified School District - Travel and Study - Grant 66, 1965 - 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Fremont Unified School District - Travel and Study - Reports, 1965 - 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Fryeburg Academy Reading Research Institute - Attachments, 1965 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Fryeburg Academy Reading Research Institute - Grant, 1965 - 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Fryeburg Academy Reading Research Institute - Reports, 1965 - 1966 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gateway School of New York - Attachments, 1965 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gateway School of New York - Grant 66, 1965 - 1968 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gateway School of New York - Reports, 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - George Washington University - Internship Program in National and Federal Educational Institutions - Grant, 1964 - 1970 (Box 13 (49574))
    - George Washington University - Internship Program in National and Educational Institutions - Reports, 1965 - 1966 (Box 13 (49574))
    - George Washington University - Internship Program in National and Federal Educational Organizations - Report, 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - George Washington University - Inventory of National Program - Grant 65, 1965 - 1968 (Box 13 (49574))
    - George Washington University - Inventory of National Program - Reports, 1965 - 1967 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Georgia, Regents of University system of - Visits Abroad - Correspondence, 1960 - 1962 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Georgia, Regents of University system of - Visits Abroad - Grant 1960, 1959 - 1960 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Class Composition Study - General Data, 1957 - 1961 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Class Composition Study - Grant, 1958 - 1960 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Class Composition Study - Grant Letter, 1957 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Class Composition Study - Publicity, 1957 - 1958 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Class Composition Study - Reports 1958 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Program to Identify Negro Students in New Haven Public Schools - Grant 64, 1963 - 1965 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Program to Identify Negro Students in New Haven Public Schools - Publicity, 1964 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Program to Identify Negro Students in New Haven Public Schools - Reports, 1965 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - School Placement - Grant 62, 1961 - 1963 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - School Placement - Supplemental Grant 63, 1963 - 1965 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - School Placement - Supplemental Grant 64, 1964 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - School Placement - Reports, 1963 - 1965 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Training and Consultation - General Correspondence, 1964 - 1965 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Training and Consulting on School Placement - Grant 65, 1964 - 1965 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Training and Consulting on School Placement - Reports, 1966 - 1968 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Workshop on School Placement - General Correspondence, 1963 - 1964 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Workshop on School Placement - General Data, 1964 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Workshop on School Placement - Grant 63, 1963 - 1965 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Gesell Institute of Child Development - Workshop on School Placement - Reports, 1963 (Box 13 (49574))
    - Goddard College, Johnson Teachers College and Lyndon Teachers College - Grant, 1957 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goddard College - Grant, 1956 - 1957 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goddard College - Publicity and Press Releases, 1956 - 1957 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goddard College - Reports, 1955 - 1958 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goddard College, Johnson Teachers College, Lyndon Teachers College - Reports, 1958 - 1960 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Better Utilization of Staff and Facilities - Grant 63, 1963 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Better Utilization of Staff and Facilities - Reports, 1963 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Fifth Year Fellowship Program of Elementary School Teacher Education - Grant, 1956 - 1959 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Fifth year Program - Preparation - Publicity, 1953 - 1956 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Fifth Year Program - Preparation - Report, 1958 - 1960 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Fifth Year Program - Preparation - Reports, 1954 - 1958 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Fifth Year Program - Preparation - Grants, 1953 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Financing Education - Grant, 1958 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Internship Program - Attachments, 1955 - 1957 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Internship Program - Grant 55, 1954 - 1955 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Internship Program - Reports, 1956 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Maryland Committee on Interracial Problems and Relations with Baltimore Committee on Human Relations - Attachments, 1955 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Maryland Committee on Interracial Problems and Relations with Baltimore Committee on Human Relations - Grant 54, 1954 - 1956 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Goucher College - Maryland Committee on Interracial Problems and Relations with Baltimore Committee on Human Relations - Reports, 1955 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Golden Gate College - Cooperative Work-Study Program in Business Administration - Attachments, 1965 - 1967 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Golden Gate College - Cooperative Work-Study Program in Business Administration - Grant 65, 1965 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Golden Gate College - Cooperative Work-Study Program in Business Administration - Reports, 1965 - 1967 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Golden Gate - Report, 1968 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Granby Public Schools - Grant, 1963 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Granby Public Schools - Report, 1964 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Great Lakes College Association - Earlham College - General Data, 1961 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Great Lakes College Association - Earlham College - Grant, 1961 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Great Lakes College Association - Earlham College - Publicity, 1961 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Greenwich Public Schools - Team Teaching Evaluation - Grants 62 and 64, 1961 - 1965 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Greenwich Public Schools - Team Teaching Evaluation Reports, 1964 - 1965 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Greenwich Public Schools - Report, 1964 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Greenwich Public Schools - Team Teaching - Report, 1965 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Greenwich Public Schools - Team Teaching - Report, 1965 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Greenwich Public Schools - Team Teaching - Grant, 1965 - 1967 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hamilton College - Teaching Machines - Supplementary Grant, 1961 - 1962 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hamilton College - Utilization of College Teaching Resources - Grant, 1958 - 1960 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hamilton College - Utilization of College Teaching Resources - Report, 1960 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hammond Public Schools - Travel and Study - Grant 65, 1965 - 1966 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hammond Public Schools - Travel and Study - Reports, 1966 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Advanced Placement - Grant 64, 1964 - 1968 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Advanced Placement - Reports, 1965 - 1967 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Cooperative Work-Study Program in Industrial Technology - Booklet, 1966 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Cooperative Work-Study Program in Industrial Technology - Grant 65, 1964 - 1968 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Cooperative Work-Study Program in Industrial Technology - Reports, 1966 - 1968 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Fifth Year Preparation Program - Virgin Islands - Conferences, 1954 - 1955 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Fifth Year Preparation Program - Virgin Islands - Grant, 1950 - 1953 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Fifth Year Preparation Program - Virgin Islands - Grant, 1954 - 1956 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Fifth Year Preparation Program - Virgin Islands - Publicity, 1953 - 1956 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Fifth Year Preparation Program - Virgin Islands - Report, 1955 - 1956 (Box 14 (49575))
    - Hampton Institute - Virgin Islands - Fifth-year program - Reports, 1953-1959 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Hampton Institute - Virgin Islands - Fifth-year program - Reports, 1963 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harrison Schools, New York - TV Instruction in reading - General data, 1961-1962 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harrison Schools, New York - TV Instruction in reading - Grant, 1960-1961 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harrison Schools, New York - TV Instruction in reading - Reports, 1964 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Hartford, University of - Grant, 1966-1968 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Hartford, University of - Reports, 1967 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Hartford, University of - Faculty visits - Grant, 1968 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Hartwick College - Interdisciplinary seminars & calendar reform - Attachments, 1966-1967 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Hartwick College - Interdisciplinary seminars & calendar reform - Grant, 1964-1970 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Hartwick College - Interdisciplinary seminars & calendar reform - Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Hartwick College - Registration study - Grant, 1963 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Admission with Advanced Standing - General data, 1954-1960 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Admission with Advanced Standing - Grant, 1954-1956 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Admission with Advanced Standing - Grants, 1954-1956 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Admission with Advanced Standing - Planing and research, 1954 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Admission with Advanced Standing - Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Committee for Programmed Instruction - Grant, 1965-1971 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Committee for Programmed Instruction - Reports, 1967 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Public policy in education - Grant, 1960-1961 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Public policy in education - Grant - Supplementary, 1960-1969 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Public policy in education - Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Economics of higher education - Grant [Confidential], 1957-1961 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Economics of higher education - Publicity, 1957 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Economics of higher education - Report, 1957 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Education reporting - Pilot studies, 1955 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Education reporting - Pilot studies - General data, 1954-1955 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Education reporting - Pilot studies - Grant, 1955-1959 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Education reporting - Pilot studies - Questionnaire, 1955-1959 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Education reporting - Pilot studies - Report, 1954 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Education reporting - Pilot studies - Report - Denver Post, 1954 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - International Association of Universities - Travel fund - November, 1954 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - International Association of Universities - Travel fund - October, 1951 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Nature of Intellectual Maturity - Grant, 1962 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Nature of Intellectual Maturity - Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Negro Administrators - Edythe J. Gaines - Grant, 1965-1966 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Negro Administrators - Edythe J. Gaines - Report, 1965-1966 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Breakthrough program - General correspondence, 1957 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Breakthrough program - Grant, 1958-1959 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Breakthrough program - Grant letter and proposal, 1956-1957 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Breakthrough program - Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase, 1956 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase - General, 1951-1954 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase - General data, 1948-1951 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase - General data, 1951-1955 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase - General data [Photograph], 1951-1952 (Box 15 (49576))
      - [Untitled], 2014.015.009; Still Image (Box SF2)
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase - General data, 1955 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase - General data, 1956 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase - Proposals, 1951-1953 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase - Report - Teacher Education Resources, 1954-1956 (Box 15 (49576))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - First phase - Report - Progress, 1951-1953 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - Second phase - General, 1954 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - Second phase - Grant letter and proposal, 1955-1957 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - Second phase - Grant letter and proposal [includes photos], 1954-1955 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - Second phase - Planning - Programs, 1953-1955 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - Second phase - Reports - Progress, 1955-1957 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Preparation - Fifth-year program - Second phase - Reports - Teacher education research, 1956-1958 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Preparing Teachers - Graducate study - Harvard Graduate School of Arts and Sciences - Grant, 1956 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Preparing Teachers - Graducate study - Harvard Graduate School of Arts and Sciences - Report, 1950-1957 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Team teaching - Grant, 1960-1965 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Team teaching - Report, 1960 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Study of major pressures on public schools - Grant, 1960 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvard University - Visits - Grant, 1963 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvey Mudd College - Improvement in curricula - Grant, 1957-1959 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvey Mudd College - Improvement in curricula - Grant, 1958 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvey Mudd College - Improvement in curricula - Meeting, 1958 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Harvey Mudd College - Improvement in curricula - Reports, 1958 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Hawaii, University of - Grant, 1956-1962 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Hawaii, University of - Evaluation, 1959 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Hicksville Public Schools - Improvement in curricula - Grant, 1958-1963 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Hicksville Public Schools - Improvement in curricula - Report, 1960-1961 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Highline College - Better Utilization of Facilities - Grant, 1962-1964 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Hofstra College - Improvement in curricula - Grant, 1958-1959 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Hofstra College - Improvement in curricula - Report, 1958 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Houston, University of - Television - General correspondence, 1961 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Houston, University of - Television - Grant, 1959 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Houston, University of - Television - Report, 1959-1963 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Hunter College - Internship program - Grants, 1954-1955 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Hunter College - Internship program - Reports, 1955 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Idaho, College of - Faculty leaves and sabbaticals - Grant, 1965-1968 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Idaho, College of - Faculty leaves and sabbaticals - Reports, 1966 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Indiana University Foundation - Institutional relations - Grant, 1958-1963 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Immaculate Heart College - Fifth-year program - General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 16 (49577))
    - Immaculate Heart College - Fifth-year program - Grant letter and supporting data, 1957-1960 (Box 16 (49577))